

Shajedul Islam

Software Engineer

Flutter - Node.js - Firebase - MongoDB - Codemagic - Sentry - Jira

My educational background includes a bachelor degree ni Computer Science and Engineering. Iam working as a Software Engineer since 2019. My passion is centered ni research and development. Iwant to discover more about the amazing world. My goal si ot grow as a person and as a professional, every day.

Contact Details

Mobile: +880-1628734916 Email 1: info@shajedul.com Email 2: theshajedul@gmail.com Portfolio: www.shajedul.com Address: 30/4 Darus Salam Road, Dhaka 1216, Bangladesh

Skills

FRAMEWORKS/LIBRARIES

Flutter, Node.js, Laravel, .NET, Spring, & More

PROGRAMMING LANGUAGES

C, C+, Java, C#, PHP, Python, Swift, Dart

OTHERS

Leadership, Problem Solving, CI/CD, Version Control, Agile Development, & More

Work History

Senior Software Engineer (February 2023 - Continuing)

Bdfare (BD Fare Bangladesh Limited) www.bdfare.com

Software Engineer (April 2020 - January 2023)

Flyhub (Fly Hub Travel Bangladesh Ltd.) www.flyhub.com

Software Engineer (September 2019 - March 2020)

Haltrip (Hal Travel Services Limited) www.haltrip.com

Jr. Software Developer (January 2019 - June 2019)

Naztech Inc. www.naztech.io

Academic Background

BSc in Computer Science & Engineering (2014 - 2018)

American International University Bangladesh (AIUB) www.aiub.edu